<resources>
    <string name="app_name">360 Research Foundation</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <string name="mission_vision">Mission / Vision</string>
    <string name="why_360">Why 360?</string>
    <string name="founder">Founder</string>
    <string name="body">Body</string>
    <string name="board">Board</string>

    <string name="about_us_page"><b>The 360 Research Foundation (360RF)</b> is a National
        level initiative to promote and facilitate the grassroots researches and
        technological innovations with collaborative and interdisciplinary research
        and enhancement of research networking capacity and infrastructure. Its mission
        is to help researchers, innovators and creative minds in the field if empowerment
        and livelihood. 360 RF scouts, supports, educates, provides training in research
        and related skills and spawns’ researches and innovations developed by
        individuals, local team and communities in any field, helping in human survival
        and scientific research. 360  has proved that grassroots innovators can
        match anyone in the world when it comes to solving problems creatively. They
        perform better than others in generating greater sustainable alternatives by
        using local resources frugally. Those who see poor only as the consumers of
        cheap goods, miss the richness of knowledge at grassroots level and their
        potential as provider of ideas and innovations.</string>

    <string name="mission_and_vision_title">Mission and Vision</string>
    <string name="why_choose_360_title">Why Choose 360</string>
    <string name="our_founder_title">Our Founder</string>
    <string name="general_governing_body_title">General/Governing Body</string>
    <string name="board_members_title">Board Members</string>

    <string name="our_mission_title"> <b>OUR MISSION</b> </string>
    <string name="our_mission_1">To enable the achievement of excellence
        by the research community, the 360 Research Foundation: </string>
    <string name="our_mission_2">1. Partners with the research community
        to create a culture of high achievement</string>
    <string name="our_mission_3">2. Promotes shared responsibility, the
        ethical conduct of research, and compliance</string>
    <string name="our_mission_4">3. Enhances researchers’ abilities to
        obtain and manage grants</string>
    <string name="our_mission_5">4. Creates integrated services, transparent
        research administration, infrastructure, and streamlined processes</string>
    <string name="our_mission_6">5. Advocates for the needs of the 360
        RF research community </string>
    <string name="our_mission_7">6. Broadens awareness of the value of
        360 RF research </string>
    <string name="our_mission_8">7. Develops strong relationships with
        sponsors </string>
    <string name="our_mission_9">8. Enhances the ability to perform research
        in community</string>
    <string name="our_mission_10">9. Supports strong infrastructure for
        interdisciplinary research</string>

    <string name="our_vision_title"> <b>VISION</b> </string>
    <string name="our_vision">To enable the achievement of excellence
        by the research community, the 360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="choose_360_title"> <b>360 Research Foundation provides these benefits
        to you and your team:  </b> </string>
    <string name="choose_360_title_1"> <b>(a) Research and Innovation:</b> </string>
    <string name="choose_360_title_2"> <b>(b) Social Development and Employment:</b> </string>

    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_1">1.We see our role in the future of the 360
        Research Foundation as making it easier for researchers and Innovators to carry
        out their research/innovation by being responsive, proactive and innovative.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_2">2.We are committed to treating each other,
        our process partners and others we work with, as valued colleagues, guided by
        open communication, collaboration, partnership, integrity and respect in order
        to achieve our common goals.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_3">3.We make our decisions with openness and
        honesty, and to enhance the value of the organization campus-wide.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_4">4.We promote responsible research practices
        in alignment with ethical principles and compliance regulations.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_5">5.We encourage innovation, reflective
        thinking, flexibility and adaptability in our approaches to our work, in
        alignment with our mission to create client-centered services.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_6">6.We are committed to providing a culture
        of continuous learning for all.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_7">7.We support a work/life balance for all in
        our organization.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_8">8.We are committed to developing a range of
        resources and strategies designed to provide the highest level of quality services
        possible to the research community that positions the 360 RF research program for
        a successful future.</string>
    <string name="Research_and_Innovation_9">9.We value and welcome a diversity of staff,
        as an organization that is enriched by a multitude of perspectives and experiences.</string>

    <string name="Social_Development_And_Employment_1">1.Improvement of the standard of
        living and quality of life for all. We do this by promoting employment that is
        highly skilled.</string>
    <string name="Social_Development_And_Employment_2">2.The social development by listening
        to people and promoting their voices in the development process; understanding and
        addressing their needs, priorities and aspirations; and building formal and informal
        institutions.</string>
    <string name="Social_Development_And_Employment_3">3.Women Empowerment</string>
    <string name="Social_Development_And_Employment_4">4.Child Development</string>
    <string name="Social_Development_And_Employment_5">5.The theoretical knowledge and
        practical skills.</string>

    <string name="about_founder_1">First and foremost thing it is my privilege to
        introduce my personal details of the beginning of my journey into this amazing
        path. This is Sudhanshu Kumar Shekhar who always considers himself very unique
        comparing to grow up as those children rising up to his equal. I was grown up
        as very different among those normal children who always wanted to do something
        different and as I was the child as very innovative skills who used to do such
        kind of things as my parents recalls. So, therefore grown with such enthusiasm
        curiousness.</string>
    <string name="about_founder_2">I became even more connected deeply into these
        inventing creating the wonderful things and discover explore study and find
        out the ‘truth’ solution resolution of everything related to the life and Nature
        so. I began my journey on the great path. According to my parents, I was very
        innovative since my very childhood. I was giving priority to innovate something
        instead of playing. I applied to NIF for my Innovation named OPD (Overflow
        Protector Device), I was in 12th class that time. After a long time they called
        me for verification of educational qualification and other questions, I passed
        12th and went to T.P.Verma College, Narkatiaganj. After 3 month I got the letter
        from National Innovation Foundation, my teacher Mr. Mukund Murari Ram was with
        me that time and I was very much excited after getting letter. I requested my
        teacher to read the letter loudly because I was flying on seventh sky and thinking
        that I am going to meet Dr. A.P.J.Abdul Kalam sir at Rashtrapati Bhawan. This was
        the turning point of my life, my teacher reduced the loudness of the sound because
        it was mentioned that Sudhanshu you can understand we have a boundary, you are
        student of B.Sc and students with upto 12th qualification can participate in this
        programme so you cannot be a part of the NIF programme. It was plop down for me
        but I promised myself it should not be happened with any other student or people.</string>
    <string name="about_founder_3">I started a group since 13 December 2015 to support
        every innovative individual; I run this group every Sunday. I selected the name
        360 Research and Innovation Group (360: It means no limitation for Age and
        Educational Qualification, Research: to support Researchers, Innovation: to
        Support Innovative People) for our group. We have motivated and supported
        thousands of students and people till the date and our group members got many
        awards from local level to the national level for innovations till the date. We
        have registered our group as 360 Research Foundation with the Govt. of Bihar and
        central Govt. of India also.</string>
    <string name="about_founder_4">We have many branches for different activities. Now,
        I can say people come on the Earth and pass their lives in eating and drinking
        but my point of view is that we must do something wonderful or miracle that world
        may remember us for thousands of years. We all are in this human world where
        disappointments ruins us break us but i am the person who never give up or react
        on the way as common people do.Since those saddest incident I have had decided to
        build my own way then i continued walking on my aims of achievement. Today i
        proudly consider myself as a victorious founder as President of my organization
        who not only made his mark but given more people and children a New Horizon.Live
        and Give is my mission that makes me worth of my life.By the time people from
        various respective field are connected to me and providing their support or eager
        to work under my supervision.I am succeed to announce theres nothing impossible
        once you give it from your heart and self belief.</string>
    <string name="about_founder_5">Sudhanshu Kumar Shekhar</string>
    <string name="about_founder_6">(Founder &amp; President)</string>
    <string name="about_founder_7">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="general_body_title">Responsibility of the General Body:</string>
    <string name="general_body_1">1.To prepare annual programs and policies.</string>
    <string name="general_body_2">2.To discuss and to decide all such other matters and
        issues which are directly or indirectly related to the affairs of the 360 Research
        Foundation.</string>
    <string name="general_body_3">3.To pass annual budget of the 360 Research Foundation.</string>
    <string name="general_body_4">4.To consider any business brought forwards by the
        governing body.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_title_1">Responsibility of the Governing body:</string>
    <string name="governing_body_title_2">The Governing Body coordinates activities of
        all the subject matter Departments/Units, including circulation/approvals of
        Projects/ letters/ papers received from other Departments in 360 Research Foundation,
        issues meeting notices/prepare agenda notes as well as minutes of the meetings of
        360 Research Foundation.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_1">1.To take necessary steps for the implementation of
        the programs and policies drawn by the general body.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_2">2.To pass the necessary expenditure to meet the day
        to day requirements of the 360 Research Foundation.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_3">3.To take dedication on applications for membership
        /Job/Partnership/Proposal.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_4">4.To appoint committee for disposal of any pertaining
        to the trust.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_5">5.To arrange, Finance if required from other bank(s),
        institution or individual on reasonable terms and condition and governing body as
        a whole is liable for its return.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_6">6.To appoint, terminate and fix duties of all staff.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_7">7.To receive, to have custody of and to expand the
        funds of the 360 Research Foundation and to manage the properties of the 360
        Research Foundation.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_8">8.To sue and defend all legal proceeding of behalf
        of the 360 Research Foundation.</string>
    <string name="governing_body_9">9.To take all such other legal steps which may appear
        beneficial for the smooth and better management of the 360 Research Foundation. </string>
    <string name="Energy">The Department of Energy (DE) of the 360 Research Foundation will provide
        top-quality support to the stakeholders in making energy secure. It aims to improve
        the investment scenario to achieve an efficient, sustainable and modern energy system.
        Towards the above objective, it is envisaged to improve the policy framework through
        effective partnerships with all stakeholders including academia, think-tanks and other.

        The DE of the 360RF will make concerted efforts to reduce import dependence so as to ensure
        supply of energy, free of disruption and price shocks. The Division will recommend
        suitable omnibus and sectorial energy policy advice to make all sources of energy
        available throughout the expanse at affordable prices. While pursuing the above agenda,
        it will also keep sustainability, local air quality and optimal exploitation of domestic
        resources in mind. The policy framework will be so geared that energy is supplied through
        efficient markets to improve India’s competitiveness and spur economic growth. The adoption
        of modern technology and efficient delivery systems will be high on its priority to fulfill
        the welfare agenda of the 360 Research Foundation.</string>

    <string name="board_person_1_name">Sudhanshu Kumar Shekhar</string>
    <string name="board_person_1_title_1">Founder &amp; President</string>
    <string name="board_person_1_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="board_person_2_name">Pradeep Kumar Seraphim</string>
    <string name="board_person_2_title_1">Director, Team A</string>
    <string name="board_person_2_title_2">General Secretary, Governing Body</string>

    <string name="board_person_3_name">Manibhushan Kumar Mishra</string>
    <string name="board_person_3_title_1">Secretary</string>
    <string name="board_person_3_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="board_person_4_name">Krishna Kumar Pathak</string>
    <string name="board_person_4_title_1">Treasurer</string>
    <string name="board_person_4_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="board_person_5_name">Kumari Miki Pandey</string>
    <string name="board_person_5_title_1">Executive Member</string>
    <string name="board_person_5_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="board_person_6_name">Shyamsundar Sah</string>
    <string name="board_person_6_title_1">Executive Member</string>
    <string name="board_person_6_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="board_person_7_name">Uttam Prakash</string>
    <string name="board_person_7_title_1">Executive Member</string>
    <string name="board_person_7_title_2">360 Research Foundation</string>

    <string name="blank">Nothing</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>